fuzzyyellowballs.com 2010-11-15

# FuzzyYellowBalls.com Privacy Policy

Fuzzy Yellow Balls is extremely proud of our Privacy Policy. Please read the entire policy below, as it is a reflection of our strong commitment to protecting you and your information while you surf our site. As young adults (and web-2.0 guys) who have grown up in the internet generation, we understand how important and valuable privacy is on the internet. _We firmly believe that when you place your information in the hands of a website, that site is obligated to protect and do no more with that information than they expressly state in the privacy policy._ Keep in mind that while we do reserve the right to change our privacy policy in the future, the overall spirit enshrined below will remain the same.

**What information do we collect?**  
Fuzzy Yellow Balls collects information from you when you subscribe to our free newsletter, register as a free member of the site, or become a paying subscriber to the FYB Premium section of the site. When subscribing to our newsletter, we ask for your first name and email address. When registering as a free member of the website, you are asked to create an account using your name (or alias), email address, and you are asked to create a password to protect your account. FYB does not have the ability to see your password, but we can reset it for you on your request. You may also visit fuzzyyellowballs.com completely anonymously.

**What do we use your information for?**  
Nothing nefarious. We ask for your email address in order to send you a weekly newsletter that lets you know what’s new on FYB, and it may contain advertisements or links to our sponsors. You may unsubscribe from the newsletter at any time by clicking on the “Unsubscribe” link at the bottom of each newsletter email. Each time we send a newsletter we are able to track how people come from the newsletter to the website. We use this information to improve the content on fuzzyyellowballs.com, and to gauge how interested people are in various aspects of the game of tennis.

**_Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the product or service you have requested from FuzzyYellowBalls.com._**

In other words, don’t worry, we aren’t going to sell your email address to some spammer. We also won’t sell the email list to any third party.

You may also choose to opt into our RSS feed updates, where we send you an update to your RSS reader or email address each time we add a new video or feature. You may unsubscribe from the RSS updates at any time. Our RSS feed subscriber list carries the same privacy policy as our email newsletter.

If you choose to become a paying subscriber of FYB Premium, we ask for your billing address and contact information. We need your billing information such as name and address in order to process your transaction. _We will not send you anything in the mail._ You may optionally provide us with your preferred telephone number so that FuzzyYellowBalls, and only FuzzyYellowBalls, can contact you proactively about any problem with your paid subscription.

**How do we protect your information?**  
When you sign up for our weekly newsletter, your contact information is not stored on FYB’s servers. It is placed directly into a highly secure database on Constant Contact’s servers which only FYB has access to. If you choose to become a free member of FuzzyYellowBalls.com, your name, alias, and email address, are stored on FYB’s secure server hosted by RackSpace. If you become a paying subscriber to the Premium section of the site, we will also store your mailing address on our secure server. SSL-Secured credit card payment processing is done via ClickBank, a trusted industry leader. Your credit card information is stored by ClickBank and is never stored by FYB. If you choose to cancel your subscription to FYB Premium at any time, your credit card information will be removed from the system by ClickBank after 30 days.

**Do we use cookies?**  
Yes. A cookie is a small file that a website places on your computer’s hard drive, through your Web browser (if you allow), that enables the site to recognize your computer and capture and remember certain information about you or your visit. Specifically, FuzzyYellowBalls.com places a cookie on your computer that allows us to remember whether or not you have signed up for our weekly newsletter. We do not use cookies to track what pages you view on FYB.com (or outside of FYB.com for that matter!), and we do not track any personally identifiable information about you using cookies.

**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**  
**We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information.** This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. For example, FYB occasionally contracts with a third party to code / develop our website. Those companies, while developing the site, might have access to our email list, but they must agree to not disclose any of the information contained within. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, and protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. 

**Third party links**  
Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

**California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**  
Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent. As part of the California Online Privacy Protection Act, all users of our site may make any changes to their information at anytime by logging into their control panel and going to the ‘Edit Profile’ page.

**COPPA Compliance**  
We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**  
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, send an email notifying you of any changes, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below. 

**This policy was last modified on 9/17/09. If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below:**

 **

Fuzzy Yellow Balls, LLC  
4545 Connecticut Ave. NW #535  
Washington, DC 20008

adam@fuzzyyellowballs.com

**
